The Seed is a horror, science fiction, comedy film directed by Sam Walker.
What starts out as a girls weekend away in the Mojave desert
becomes a tale of horror, death and alien invasion.
Heather, played by Sophie Vavasseur.
Deidre, played by Lucy Martin.
Charlotte, played by Chelsea Edge.
Cowboy, played by Anthony Edridge.
Edna, played by Shirley Barchou Pisani.
Brett, played by Jamie Wittebrood.
The Seed is the 2021 science fiction body horror feature film
directorial debut of Sam Walker, who also wrote the script.
The movie premiered in the United States at Beyond Fest, after which it
was released to Shudder as one of its original films.
The film received mixed to positive reviews.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and thought_provoking.